this u-turns about pyramids so here it
这个关于金字塔的掉头，所以在这里
是一个基本的金字塔，你可以改变
this u-turns about pyramids so here it
is a basic pyramids you can vary the
比例和改变类型
您正在生产的金字塔，所以这是
is a basic pyramids you can vary the
proportions and change the type of
最简单的是一个例子
那是更深的容忍度
proportions and change the type of
pyramid that you're producing so this is
平行于脊椎而下垂
这些是基于默认的，所以这些
pyramid that you're producing so this is
the most simple here's an example of one
折痕在脊柱上收敛
这次关上拐角处提起
the most simple here's an example of one
that's tolerance deeper this one is
平行于脊椎被卡住
它也以不同的方式关闭
that's tolerance deeper this one is
stuck down parallel to the spine whereas
这有六个折痕，而另一个
只是在角落的折痕
stuck down parallel to the spine whereas
these ones are based on default so these
金字塔，这个必须有折痕
脊柱上方还有其他
these ones are based on default so these
the creases converge on the spine as it
变化，所以这是一个
不对称的金字塔非常复杂
the creases converge on the spine as it
closes down the corner lift up this time
计算，但它们相当有趣
这是另一个变化
closes down the corner lift up this time
is stuck down parallel to the spine so
实际上是一个圆锥体，但是是一样的
作为金字塔的原理
is stuck down parallel to the spine so
it closes up in a different way also
平行于脊椎卡住
没有任何角度折痕
it closes up in a different way also
this has six creases whereas the other
角，但基本形状相同
这是一个伸展的金字塔，这是一个
this has six creases whereas the other
just has creases on the corners of the
平行折叠教程六与半
在这两端的金字塔蔓延
just has creases on the corners of the
pyramid this one has to have creases
骆驼用不对称制成
金字塔和脖子也许是
pyramid this one has to have creases
above the spine there are other
覆盖在里面的对折件
教程艾滋病等等
above the spine there are other
variations so there's and this is an
基本的金字塔已经城堡
给骆驼很僵硬
variations so there's and this is an
asymmetric pyramids quite complicated to
形状，以便您可以切掉，所以我会
只是告诉你如何使自己变得规律
asymmetric pyramids quite complicated to
calculate but they're quite quite fun
简单的金字塔取一个基片折叠
将其完全折半
calculate but they're quite quite fun
this is a another variation this is
那你可以拿半张卡
你需要一个指南针，你需要一个计分
this is a another variation this is
actually a cone but it's the same
用一把尺子和通常的剪刀
用胶水把罗盘标记放在哪里
actually a cone but it's the same
principle as the pyramid again it's
你要把重点画一个
半圆越大，
principle as the pyramid again it's
stuck down parallel to the spine just
越恭喜你，金字塔可以成为你
然后调整之间的差距
stuck down parallel to the spine just
hasn't got any angle creases making
点和指南针上的铅笔
间隙越大，金字塔越平坦
hasn't got any angle creases making
corners but it's the same basic shape so
差距越小，越多
如此陡峭而尖锐
corners but it's the same basic shape so
this is a stretch pyramid it's a
取决于你想要什么类型的金字塔
所以做第一个标记并测量一个
this is a stretch pyramid it's a
parallel fold tutorial six with half a
让我们再来一次艺术再做一次，这些
是金字塔的四个底面
parallel fold tutorial six with half a
pyramid on each end in this spread the
所以现在需要四个基础
在那些标记之间得分
pyramid on each end in this spread the
camel is made with an asymmetric
和点所在
指南针是我要注意的一个
camel is made with an asymmetric
pyramids and the neck is maybe the
脱销到那
二三四和最后一个你会
pyramids and the neck is maybe the
counter folded piece that is covered in
也需要两条直线
将其粘贴到页面的选项卡的位置
counter folded piece that is covered in
tutorial AIDS and so whole chunks of the
你将会是，所以我们就把他们
彼此相邻所以有一个
tutorial AIDS and so whole chunks of the
basic pyramid have been Castle
还有其他这些其他优势
只需要直接切断就可以了
basic pyramid have been Castle
to give the camel there is a very rigid
不妨将它们与
尺子，所以你会得到一个不错的直切
to give the camel there is a very rigid
shape so you can cut pieces away so I'll
然后这最后一面
需要一个粘贴标签来拉整个
shape so you can cut pieces away so I'll
just show you how to make make a regular
东西变成形状，所以我们将其切开
裁切标签，您需要注意
just show you how to make make a regular
simple pyramid take a base sheet fold it
金字塔顶部的角度和
确保标签的角度为
simple pyramid take a base sheet fold it
in half crease it really thoroughly and
将适合其中，然后您
可以减少这条线，你需要
in half crease it really thoroughly and
then you can take half a piece of card
这些的胶合标签这些得分
线
then you can take half a piece of card
you need a compass you need a scoring
正确的折痕不会忘记
折痕是制表符所在的位置
you need a compass you need a scoring
tool a ruler and the usual scissors and
将整个内容粘贴到页面上
然后你把它粘起来
tool a ruler and the usual scissors and
glue so take the compass mark where
确保那些折痕真的很好
然后用胶水将其塑形
glue so take the compass mark where
you're going to put the point draw a
粘在上面然后粘上
因此，在将其粘贴到页面之前
you're going to put the point draw a
semicircle the bigger the circle that
确保您正在切割并粘合
实际折叠成平底
semicircle the bigger the circle that
the flatter thee the pyramid can be you
他要在下面粘的床单
看看并确保他们不会
the flatter thee the pyramid can be you
then adjust the the gap between the
重叠，然后就会粘住
这样下去，你实际上并没有
then adjust the the gap between the
point and the pencil on your compass the
需要测量它要去的地方
坚持下去，只是要确保
point and the pencil on your compass the
bigger the gap the flatter the pyramid
两个标签之间的折痕位于
线并确保其他油脂
bigger the gap the flatter the pyramid
will be the smaller the gap the more
也在那根脊柱线上，然后你
可以同时将它们粘合在一起
will be the smaller the gap the more
steep and pointy it will be so it all
它只是确保两个选项卡是一个
在每一侧确保他们指出
steep and pointy it will be so it all
depends what type of pyramid you wanting
金字塔的角平齐
用那条线，然后你可以
depends what type of pyramid you wanting
so make the first mark and measure off a
将其关闭并向下按
您在设计中拥有它，您可能会
so make the first mark and measure off a
let's round the art do it again so these
想要隐藏在某些东西下面的东西
图像或其他小v形折叠或
let's round the art do it again so these
are the four base sides of the pyramid
以便您打开页面时
消失在金字塔下或你
so there's the four bases now you need
这样处理，这样您就可以
看起来更好的错觉
so there's the four bases now you need
to score between those those marks and
与页面齐平，我将向您展示
很少有商业的，所以这很棒
to score between those those marks and
the and the points where the point of
世界和
首先传播的是几个金字塔
the and the points where the point of
the compass was one I'll just note this
下一个我有一个是蓝色的两个，
金字塔是平行于
the compass was one I'll just note this
off store onto that
脊椎你可以看到它的刚性形状
是你可以减少很多
two three four and the last one you'll
它仍然保持其形状和
实际上里面还有两个金字塔
two three four and the last one you'll
also need two straight scored lines
它都平行折叠，您可以看到
这些在脊椎上的褶皱
also need two straight scored lines
where the tabs that glue it to the page
在这种情况下需要平行折叠
向内而不是向外
where the tabs that glue it to the page
you're going to be so we just put them
终于这本书飞来了
Pennock在这种情况下的机器
you're going to be so we just put them
adjacent to each other so there's one
飞机是基于基本的盒子
是教程14，但如果您查看
adjacent to each other so there's one
there's the other these other edges will
是金字塔的平面的鼻锥
那是一个平行折叠的金字塔
there's the other these other edges will
just need to be cut off straight so
粘在飞机的两壁上
所以那是金字塔而不是用作
just need to be cut off straight so
might as well just cut them off with the
金字塔，但它的一部分是相同的
用作另一部分的机制
might as well just cut them off with the
ruler so you get a nice straight cut one
设计，仅此而已
在这本Mod书中有更多关于它们的信息
and then this last side you're going to
弹出式设计和纸张力学
您
and then this last side you're going to
need a gluing tab to to pull the whole
您